Heat. Heat.
[Music]
Hello, good evening, good day everybody
and welcome to the Ask a Widget Show.
This is another unscheduled episode
because of the situation that we
currently find ourselves in and I hope
you're all doing very well. I just
watched the address to the nation by
Prime Minister Narendra Modi. It was
very interesting to say the least and
I'm sure I'm going to have questions
about that in today's episode. And I was
supposed to have this start the episode
at 8:00 p.m. today, but then it it
emerged that Prime Minister Modi was
going to do the speech at 8:00 p.m. So
it made sense for me to move it to 9:00
p.m. So here we are and thank you so
much for being on this live stream. Let
me see who all is there on the live
stream. I can see Shravani Man Cheddar
Anand Pai Gojo Lone Travel Guru Rashmir
Ratur Barka Batra Nationalist Arpit Jane
Amandep Singh Anand Chandak Pranav
Pavish Shrina Dikant Bish Parapati Panda
9000 SP Ishan WMA Vishal Jwal
Chaitananya Kai Angeli Sinha
Sinha Parasav Kundu Chira Parker Aish
Mishra Mudra Makwana Jit Singh Abinav
Tutti Mishra, Nikil, Negi, Rushi,
Shashank, Koshik, Pravin, Na, Hardik,
Papati, Amitg, Davik, Shrian, Himanch,
Shukla, Vishal, Kumar, Pray, all from
Kolkata, Vehav, Shindai, Akash, Ba,
Karan, Nalawat, NGL, Knight, Pratamesh,
Tjas, Shash,
Patandikar, uh, Anand, Mi, Yatagiri,
Amit, Gag, Event Countdown, Vidant,
Shukla, and everybody else. Thank you so
much for being in the live stream. I'll
not spend so much time greeting you all.
Please let's get going with the
questions. Please ask me your questions.
I'm sure you have a lot to ask and we
have a lot to
discuss. So, okay, adventure with Saraj
starts the questioning. The first
question is what do you think about
Prime Minister Narendra Modi's speech?
It was a very interesting speech and I
think you know what what I need to
actually do is I need to play the speech
in the background and I need to react to
it. I've never done a reaction video to
anybody. I think it is time for me to do
make such a video. Now I don't have the
speech right now. I'll have to download
it and play it or something like that.
I've never done that before. So maybe
I'll do it tomorrow. How about I do a
live stream tomorrow in which I react in
real time to Prime Minister Narendra
Modi's speech because it was about 20 22
minutes long. Very important points were
made in that speech. He was visibly
angry and a lot of subtleties and
nuances in that speech. So I think I'll
do an episode again tomorrow. I mean
completely out of unscheduled but let's
do it. I'll do another episode tomorrow,
another live stream tomorrow in which
I'll react to Prime Minister Modi's
speech segment by segment. But overall,
let's let's answer the question today. I
think it was very interesting the
speech. Prime Minister Modi uh made many
points that we have been discussing the
past few days, right? Uh he made it very
clear that uh over a 100 Pakistani
terrorists have been eliminated.
He said that many uh terror uh
masterminds uh have been eliminated.
Right? He also said he made it very
clear to the Pakistanis that this is
this so-called ceasefire is a pause. We
have put a pause to think to this thing
because you came to us and you begged
for a pause. So, we have put a pause to
our military actions and we're going to
now and we made the did the pause
because you promised us that you're
going to mend your ways. So, we're going
to hold you to it and we're going to
observe you, we're going to scrutinize
your activities and actions very closely
and the moment you you show any sign or
signal of going back to your old ways,
we're going to resume operation. So,
it's just a pause. That's what he said.
He also said that uh he said that terror
and talks cannot go together. He said
that terror and trade cannot go
together. He said blood and water cannot
flow together. Very clear, right?
He so these are the points that he made.
He also made a statement. He said to the
larger to the world at large whoever is
out there beyond the subcontinent he
said that you know if you want India and
Pakistan to talk to hold talks then yeah
we can talk but we if we talk to
Pakistan we're going to talk about
terrorism if we talk to Pakistan we're
going to talk about P and nothing
else. It's very interesting what he said
to the rest of the world. What does he
mean by the rest of the
world? What does he mean? That's the
question. And it's also really
interesting to note what or who Prime
Minister Modi did not mention in his
address to the nation. Who is it that
has tried to take credit for the
so-called
ceasefire? It is US President Donald
Trump, right? He has tried to take
credit for the ceasefire.
And Mr. Narendra Modi did not mention
the United States. He did not mention
President
Trump. Right? So he clearly disagrees
with what Trump is saying. And US
Secretary of State Marco Rubio had said
he had stated that India and Pakistan he
he he announced this the guy that India
and Pakistan have decided have have
agreed to hold
talks at a neutral venue of some kind.
So prime minister Modi said to the world
at large that yeah we can talk to
Pakistan but if we talk to Pakistan
we'll talk only about terrorism and P
and nothing
else and terrorism and talks cannot go
together so first we will need to see
how Pakistan behaves right and Trump had
tweeted about this thing a couple of
days ago that uh India and Pakistan are
now going to have a ceasefire and you
will know we all know that whenever
President Trump tweets anything about
India. Prime Minister Modi very rapidly
acknowledges that with a great amount of
warmness on Twitter itself. Right? And
this time Prime Minister Modi has
ignored Trump's
tweet and if you watched the speech the
address of Prime Minister Modi he looked
visibly angry at times. Now what was he
visibly angry about? Obviously about the
Indians who were killed in the Pahelgam
attack. Sure, he was angry about
Pakistan and Pakistan's behavior for
sure. But I think there was another
element or aspect or dimension to his
anger. He was angry at something more
than Pakistan. I think he was angry
angry about Trump, Trump's
interference. Trump came in the way.
Trump actually said that he Trump
actually threatened India that we're
going to end trade with India. That's
the threat that he gave. And I can I can
prove it to you. Give me a second. Let
me bring that on the screen. I will I
will put that on the screen. So, here is
uh just give me a
second. Okay, let's put this on the
screen. So, this is what the media has
not really highlighted the Indian media.
I don't know what they do. It's it's
come out on the times of India over here
as you can see as a kind of footnote. No
uh US stop nuclear conflict blah blah
blah blah blah blah etc etc etc right
more more more and millions of all that
he's talking about and then what look at
this paragraph I think nobody in the
Indian media has has noticed this or
paid attention to this Trump further
confirmed ongoing trade negotiations
with both India and Pakistan stating
that we are going to do a lot of trade
with Pakistan we're going to do a lot of
trade with India we are negotiating with
India right now and uh one second where
did that go it's interesting trade we're
going to soon negotiate with
Pakistan interesting where is that
particular part of the thing
uh huh okay here he also claimed Trump
that US trade leverage played a role in
diffusing tensions between the
neighboring countries stating we helped
a lot and we also helped with trade I
said come on we're going to do a lot of
trade with you guys let's stop it. Let's
stop it. If you stop it, we doing trade.
If you don't stop it, we are not going
to do any trade. Do you understand that?
If you don't stop it, we're not going to
do any trade. People have never really
used trade the way I used it. But that I
can tell you and all of a sudden they
said, so he threatened, forget about
Pakistan, he threatened India that if
you don't stop what you're doing to
Pakistan, we are not going to do any
trade. Which essentially means that the
Americans will impose trade sanctions on
India.
Do you see what Trump has
done? He
threatened to impose trade sanctions on
India. We will not do any trade with you
anymore. That's what he
said. That can destroy a nation's
economy. Pakistan doesn't matter whe
whatever he said to Pakistan. Pakistan
was not the one uh you know striking at
at the other country. We were the ones
who had Pakistan at at our
mercy and Trump came in the way and
saved
Pakistan and then he claimed that he he
has achieved this great uh great
ceasefire. Right? So Mr. Modi has Mr.
Modi was clearly very angry about this.
And I promise you this my friends,
Trump will in some shape or form or some
way pay some kind of price for this what
he has done in the long run. He has
another four, three and a half, four
years to go, right? This is a long-term
thing. The the world doesn't uh it
doesn't, you know, forget about the
short term. the the world is a long-term
game and Trump is well this will come
back to to he will he will see reminders
of this
somewhere the US will have to pay some
kind of price for what they've done here
for giving Pakistan a lifeline so uh
that's what I can say but let's take
some more questions come on let's do
that doesn't India export
pharmaceuticals to the US yeah but but
please look at the bigger picture that's
not how trade works
Um uh anonymous scientist says that
interestingly there was no mention of
Trump or his administration in Prime
Minister Modi's address to the nation.
That's exactly what I just discussed.
Right? Mr. Modi made it a point to not
mention Donald Trump or his
administration or the US in his address
to the nation. It it is very notable and
it is uh very interesting. Right.
Okay, I'll not take questions about
astrophysics today. We're we're
discussing Pakistan and this issue, the
three-day war. Uh Hari Vin says, "How
many units of Akash and S400 systems do
we need to guard India's borders?
It is very evident uh after the 3-day
war has paused that we have sufficient
units of Akash and S400 systems to guard
our western border with Pakistan from
the north all the way to the south all
the way from Ladak all the way to Kach
in Gujarat western India. All of that we
have been able to completely per almost
perfectly safeguard it. So that is taken
care of. Now we have another bigger
border. I mean if you want to look at
the map in case you're not familiar with
India's map but let's do it. Let's
illustrate the point I am trying to make
here. Let's take a look at the
map. Here is map. So we have this
western border with the terrorist with
the artificial ter temporary terrorist
nation uh which is all the way from
Ladak Jammu and Kashmir. You have
Himachal Pradesh I don't know not really
Himachal Pradesh but Hiana Punjab all
those regions then Rajasthan large state
then Gujarat another large state all the
way to Sir Creek in the western most
part of Gujarat Kach right so all of
that we have now proven that it is
perfectly well defended uh through this
multi-layered air defense system that we
have which has Akash which has Barak
which has S400 which has the L70 gun
which as man pads which is which is pura
all these different systems integrated
together in a multi-layered air defense
system so we have so so before I I go
further with that let me say something
my friends do you people realize what's
what has been proved to the world in the
past in this three-day
war the world will now
notice that India has the world's best
air defense system. The world's best
battle tested air defense system tested
over and over again in just 3
days. The Indian air defense system, I
don't know what it its name is. It
doesn't have an integrated name, but the
Indian air defense system is superior to
Israel's Iron Dome. We proved it over
the course of this three-day war. The
Pakistanis threw everything they had at
us and we brought everything down.
Nothing went through. Not a single
drone, not a single short-range missile,
medium-range missile, whatever range
missile. They even launched a missile at
Delhi. That was brought down. Everything
they tried was brought brought down.
They tried to hit more than 25 maybe
more than 30 Indian cities, civilian
centers. They tried to hit schools and
colleges and temples and gurudaras and
whatnot, right? They tried to hit
everything they could and nothing was
touched. They tried it over and over and
over again. In just one night, they
launched more than 500
drones. Every single one was brought
down. India has the world's best battle
tested air defense system. Superior to
the Iron Dome system of the Israelis.
superior to anything else that has been
actually battle tested. Incredible. Now
coming back to the
question. All right. So here we are. Now
we have another border with the actual
larger threat which is China. This is
the India Tibet border. Right? All the
way from Arunachal Pradesh all the way
to Uttarakhand. And then we if you go
further north in the Ladak region uh we
have Singinjang. what the Chinese call
sing. So that's another significantly
large uh border. If we add up the length
of the border, it is uh definitely
longer than the border that we have with
the temporary nation.
Now I'm not sure what the situation of
concerning air defense is along the
India, Tibet and India uh Chinese
occupied territory border but we will
need the same quality and quantity same
quality of air defense but probably a
larger
quantity because the Chinese may pose a
different kind of threat. They may have
different kinds of they definitely will
have different kinds of weapons compared
to what the Pakistanis have right the
Pakistanis what do they have in terms of
aircraft fighter planes they have uh the
F-16 which is an 1970s aircraft but the
Americans have been upgrading it so it
is I'm sure it's a pretty good aircraft
let's not write it off it's a pretty
good aircraft the F-16 and they have the
Chinese
JF17 which is a much better aircraft
much more modern
aircraft and those threats have been
neutralized by India We saw it over the
past three days. Now the Chinese have
fifth generation generation fighter
planes. Two at two different kinds of
fifth generation fighter generation
fighter planes. The J the J20 I think
it's called and there's one more
apparently and they have other other
kinds of fighter planes. They have I'm
sure many more fighter planes
numerically than the Pakistanis have and
they have other maybe superior missiles
what the Pakistanis have and superior
drones perhaps. So uh so we haven't our
air defense system hasn't been tested
against the Chinese but we our armed
forces obviously will know very well
what the Chinese have. It's not like we
are blind and we have no idea what the
Chinese are up to. We have been studying
the Chinese threat for a very very long
time. We have professionals who whose
entire job is to study China. So we have
that that's going on and I'm sure that
we have the technology now. It's very
clear we have some of the best
technology in the world. I think the
Indian missiles and Indian air defense
system indigenous one is I think
superior to anything anybody has
anywhere in the
world. We can actually say that now
after the battle testing it underwent
for 3 days and three nights. So I'm sure
that we can very well take care of the
Chinese threat. The Chinese must be
really worried right
now. The whole world is now looking at
India with a different set of eyes. In
just 3 days the whole perception has
changed and it obviously has to change.
I think numerically we will need more
more numbers of Akash systems, more
numbers of S400 systems, more numbers of
whatever else. The border is longer. We
also have to consider the geographical
position of our friendly nation Nepal
for instance. Let me put that on the
screen once again. Let's take a look.
So in case there's a war in the future
between India and China, the Chinese if
if things don't go well don't go well
for the Chinese they may try and
leverage Nepal. They may try to come
through Nepal also. We also have to keep
that in mind. I'm sure we are keeping
that in mind.
So Nepal could become Nepal, you know,
you could say the British uh left Nepal
independent because they wanted a buffer
state between uh territory that the
Chinese were interested in and British
India, British occupied India. So Nepal
is kind of still occupies the position
of kind of a buffer state and the
Chinese may try to leverage that if they
can if there's a war with India which
doesn't go well for them. So we will
have to consider this entire border.
It's like we have to defend Nepal also
against China right we have to defend
all the way from the northernmost part
of Ladak all the way to the eastern most
part of Pradesh including Bhutan
including Sikkim including Nepal in
including Uttarakhan Himachel everything
else that's what how we have to approach
the potential threat so I'm sure we will
need many more units of Akash S400
systems than we have deployed on the
western border and the the units that
are deployed on the western border will
have to stay there and now we will have
to uh reformulate our approach because
the Pakistanis will have learned
something from the past 3 days from the
absolute whooping they got over over the
past 3 days. So now battle strategies
and tactics and perceptions and
everything else they evolve. It always
evolves. Every new battle is a new day
and a new new set of uh parameters that
you have to consider. Right.
Okay. Okay. Okay. I can see questions.
All right. Let's see this. Mlvin says,
"So Trump said on Truth Social that
after a thousand years he will find a
solution for Kashmir. Is the
thousand-year thing a hit towards us? Is
he trying to make Kashmir a global
issue?" No, I don't think Trump is
interested in making Kashmir a global
issue issue. But he's focusing on
Kashmir right now. Let's understand why
Trump has suddenly decided to focus on
Kashmir. Let's understand what actually
happened. So Trump had made the promise
to his voters
h that he will end the Ukraine war on
the first day of his
presidency. That's the promise he had
made and he has failed miserably.
at
that
then that didn't work and now the
Americans are no longer interested in
mediating in the Ukraine Russia thing
and they now seem to be looking at
Ukraine from a purely financial and
resources perspective the the minerals
deal they've done so they are okay with
letting the war go on now it looks like
so Trump has failed miserably at his
promise uh about ending the Ukan war
when it comes to uh the Gaza situation,
the Israel Gaza war. Well, things aren't
going well there. Also, he has not able
he's not been able to end that conflict
or decisively turn it in favor of
whoever he wants it to. And uh his
personal equation or relationship with
uh Netanyahu has also seems to have
soured. So even that's not going well
for him. So he's looking for a win
somewhere and he and he has decided that
I'm going to arm twist India into giving
me this this win I want. So here we go
public of India of America American
voters look what I did. I just walked in
and I ended the conflict. I made did a
ceasefire and uh this thousand-y year
thing I just don't get what it means. Is
he trying to talk about the thousand
years in which the uh Arabic and Turic
uh marauders tried to invade India and
some of them occupied India for some
time? Is he talking about that? Or is he
saying that it's not our conflict, it's
a forever conflict and maybe if I stop
it then I'm a great great great
Mahapurush or something. Not sure. I
don't really care what he's trying to
say. Now the real question
is what see JD Wans Trump's number
number two uh the vice president he had
made the statement that you know this
this conflict India Pakistan war etc
it's none of our business it's not
America's business we need to stay out
of it and just about 24 hours later they
this they they step in and they announce
that they've ended the conflict they've
made India and Pakistan agree to a
ceasefire so what caused this sudden
U-turn from the Americans What caused
that? That's the interesting question,
isn't it? What really happened?
Something happened that that sent the
Americans in a panic. And it's being
speculated that India hit various uh
nuclear uh storage sites of the
Pakistanis where they have stored
nuclear
warheads. The Americans seem to be very
interested in those warheads for some
reason more than the Chinese. So
apparently one one scenario one
possibility is that India hit Pakistani
nuclear warhead storage sites and maybe
destroyed some war warheads maybe
radiation leaked out and that's why the
Americans have come to mop things up and
maybe apparently the Pakistanis may have
made some threats to the Americans that
we will cross the nuclear threshold and
the Americans panicked maybe that's
another scenario but what really
happened I think the Americans started
panicking once we started hitting the
Nur Khan air base in 30 minutes we hit
nine air bases right we had completely
neutralized Pakistan's air defenses and
in the last 30 minutes of the war the
Indian air force crossed over into into
the Pakistani airspace or into Pakistani
territory cratered all the
runways and started hitting air base
after air base we hit nine air bases in
30 minutes with complete air dominance
once you crater the runways of the of
the enemy their planes can't take
off and
we we did very very damaging hits to
places like Nurh Khan, Nurh Khan Air
Base. Now here's the deal. Some of these
air bases have F-16s, American
F-16s. Now do you know the deal with
America and Pakistan? These F-16s are
given to Pakistan but the Americans own
the
F-16s and they have the Americans have
personnel who are always on location in
Pakistan and who never let the F-16s off
out of their eyes. So in every Pakistani
air base that has F-16s stationed there,
you will have a bunch of American
technicians and and
personnel who are in charge of
babysitting and safeguarding the F-16s.
Which means that if the Pakistanis
launch F-16s towards India, it is with
the full cooperation of the Americans.
It also means that when when India hits
those air bases which have
F-16s well people can die. What kind of
people? American
personnel. Did that
happen? Did that happen in the past 3
days? Is that why the Americans said
enough is
enough? My question is why do the
Americans have so much of an interest in
Pakistan? So, you know, this is the kind
of thing that's that's happened. Some
people said there's a nuclear leak. I'm
seeing seeing the comments and all that,
but there's I'm sure there are multiple
reasons for this. But the Americans gave
the Pakistanis a lifeline. And Mr. Modi
is extremely angry about this. It's very
clear. Sun G says something very
interesting. And I like what Suna G is
saying here. Trump gave India an easy
way out of buying overexpensive American
weapons. We should accept this large big
ginormous beautiful
gift. I said some time ago that Mr. Modi
is very angry, clearly angry. I I could
see that during his address to the
nation and he made it a point not to
mention his good friend President Trump
and not to mention the United States in
his address to the nation. He refused to
give the Americans any credit for what's
for the ending or the pause in our
military operations. Right? And Trump
has saved the Pakistanis. He has saved
their
skins when we had the chance to end this
once and for all. And the nuclear
blackmail, the nuclear threat had been
wiped out. There was no question of any
nuclear threat. The Pakistanis was were
begging for their lives. If if they
really were to use the nuclear weapons,
they would have used them
earlier and even if they tried, they
would have failed because our air
defense would have taken everything out.
That's what the Pakistanis came face to
face with. So they they they were
begging and pleading for their lives and
and Trump saved their skins. Right now
Mr. Modi, if you know anything about
him, he doesn't
forget, right?
Trump is going to pay some price for
this. He had declared unilaterally some
time ago when Mr. Modi went to
Washington DC. Trump had declared that
India is going to buy
F-35s. Well, why don't you try and make
India buy F-35s now?
H try and make India buy buy F-35s.
Those overpriced flying trash
bins. We're not buying any
F-35s. Not going to happen. So yes, this
is a very perceptive
statement very perceptive and I agree
with this.
Paris says, "Will nuclear radiation
reach northern India through air?" Which
which which nuclear radiation? Which
nuclear radiation? We haven't hit any
nuclear reactors? Nuclear fallout
happens when you either have an
explosion, atomic explo, nuclear
explosion of any kind in atmosphere in
the atmosphere or it happens when you
break open a nuclear reactor and there's
a meltdown like what happened in
Chernobyl or Fukushima. That's when you
have nuclear radiation uh in the air.
There's no such thing. If there is any
leakage, it is localized leakage. See, I
showed yesterday we I did a live stream
yesterday in which I showed what's the
melting point of uranium and what's the
melting point point of
plutonium and what's the evaporation
point of uranium and plutonium. So, both
could melt if you have nuclear warheads
that we have hit with the bramos or
whatever we have hit it causes a lot of
gives off a lot of heat. So the fuel the
the whether it's uranium or plutonium it
may have melted but it won't have
evaporated right so it won't go into the
atmosphere maybe the the warheads would
have fragmented and maybe it the the the
fragments of the file material may have
fallen over a wide area in Rahul Pindi
or wherever else that's not our problem
it's not reaching us
so so worry not my friends worry
thought
okay Prashant Singh Johan says will poke
come back in two to three months
astrologers consider a high possibility
of it I don't know about astrology okay
I have zero understanding of astrology
so I'll not comment about that I had
made a prediction when the war started
that that the borders will change in 14
days looks like my prediction is going
to fall flat but let's see I will be
happy if it comes in three two to three
months I'll be happy uh it looked like
it would have come in the last 3 days
actually. Yeah. So, uh we will see about
that. We will
see. Who who who
who says why did India not retaliate to
the drone attacks from the idiot
Pakistanis after the ceasefire
understanding after the cessation
temporary cessation of Indian military
activities? How long are we going to
accept
this? Yes. So apparently the Indian
media has been reporting uh that the
Pakistanis have been indulging in
ceasefire
violations. We should we should hit them
hard if they do that. Okay. So now uh
understand something. Should I say this?
Should I not say
this? Look
um Pakistan was begging for mercy. They
were on their knees pleading for mercy,
right? and the Americans stepped in and
they we have done the ceasefire the
so-called pause in our military
activities. Do you think the Pakistanis
are were in a position
to to uh violate ceasefire? Maybe we
were rubbing it in on them and they were
trying to respond. Poss. I'm just I'm
just completely speculating. Okay, this
is pure speculation. It may or may not
have anything to do with with the real
world. I'm just saying. But yeah, if the
Pakistanis are are breaking the
ceasefire, we should punish them very
thoroughly and very very uh hard for
their ceasefire violations.
Absolutely. All right. Uh let's here we
have it. In spite of having the worst
education system, how do we manage to
develop such impressive technology? We
have the worst education system, but we
have the best minds. Friends, imagine if
we improve the education system even 30%
what this nation is going to achieve. We
succeed despite all the friction, all
the problems we have our our system has
created for
us. Imagine if we have an education
system on par with what you have in the
developed nations. Imagine what the
people of this country will achieve. I I
cannot imagine how how this country will
change.
It will be the greatest country in human
history. Right? Despite having all these
problems, despite having this super
mediocre education system which seeks
out and destroys talent and rewards
mediocrity, still we
have still we have people, engineers,
scientists, etc. who develop the best
technology in the world while being paid
peanuts. Right?
So we need to change this. It will
unleash the potential of this nation.
What can I
say? Rohan says, "What do you think that
CNN's false articles of saying the Rafal
has been of has been downed? Is it a way
of the Americans to arm twist India to
buy F-35?" Okay, what do I think of
this? CNN has been saying this. Many
other American think tanks and
journalists have been saying they have
been verbating repeating what the
Pakistanis have been claiming. Now
whatever claims we have made we have
given evidence of that incontrovertible
evidence right we haven't officially
said that we brought down x number of
Pakistani airplanes we haven't said that
now the the the claims the Pakistanis
have made have they provided a shred of
evidence a shred they've provided some
social media posts some Reddit posts of
some some plane crash in some past date
maybe 2011 or 2014 or 2017 or 2022 or
something old plane crashes, old debris
they are showing and they're trying to
photoshop them to make them look like
they are current things. Have they shown
a single piece of credible, verifiable,
incontrovertible evidence to back it up?
Zero. Nothing. So the CNN is lying. Now
the question is why are the Americans
lying? Respected American analysts are
lying right now and and claiming that
India lost five aircraft in the first
day and all that sort of utter uh
manure, horse manure. Why they doing
this? It's because
uh possibly the Pak
see
maybe if
if if we downed Pakistani air aircraft
then it means that our Russian and
French technology brought those aircraft
down right and the Pakistanis used
Chinese and American technology. So you
have to build that up. So it's it's
about damage control. It's about
perception management. It's it's to the
Americans and the French don't get
along. I'll tell you that the French do
not have a good opinion of the
Americans. The French actually see the
Americans as adversaries. Okay? And
there is no interoperability between the
French intelligence agencies and the US.
Very little.
So the Americans
um are obviously playing this game of
perception management. U India is not an
official US ally, right? So and Pakistan
historically has been an official US
ally and the Pakistanis use F-16s and a
lot of other American equipment and uh
you have American technicians on
Pakistani air bases 24x7 by 365 tending
to those F-16s, right?
So yeah, there's a lot of reasons why
the Americans have been make, you know,
peddling these blatant lies which have
zero
verifiability. And if they think this is
going what's going to make us buy the
F-35, it's going to have the exact
opposite effect. I think what India
should do is buy a whole bunch of Rafal.
The Rafal clearly works. Yeah. buy a
whole bunch of Rafal the 4.5 generation
fighter plane with all those long range
super longrange missiles buy 100 buy 200
of those or if you don't want to buy
Rafals maybe you can think of the
Russian Suko 57 in case it is any good
maybe it is some good possibly right let
the experts decide how good or how not
so good or whatever what the quality is
and which is best suited for us we know
how to use the Rafal we've been using it
for using it for quite some time I think
it's a pretty impressive aircraft from
whatever I know whatever I Okay. So
maybe we should just buy the the Rafal
in large numbers and in the meanwhile in
the meanwhile develop the advanced
medium combat aircraft the fifth
generation fighter plane we're
developing. I promise you the only issue
is the fighter jet otherwise we're going
to bring you know we're going to put out
a top class aircraft. I think now at
least Indians should trust India's
engineers and scientists and weapons
designers after what we have seen the
past 3 days. So yeah, that's what I
think about this.
Now geopolitical duet says, "Don't you
think we should have a proper tool or
mechanisms like China or Western
countries to propagate our narrative? We
should we should have our own propaganda
outlets. The Chinese have multiple
propaganda outlets. the Global Times and
whatever and whatever whatever the the
West has this whole hoorde, this whole
ecosystem of propaganda outlets like the
BBC, like the Guardian, like the CNN,
like Fox News, like like like New York
Times, Washington Post, the list just
goes on and on. We have nothing. Why the
hell do we have nothing? So, yeah, that
needs to happen. Absolutely needs to
happen. And Ary Singh says ceasefire
violation. Apparently, there's a
ceasefire violation happening right now.
I think we should hammer the Pakistanis
hard. Hammer hammer them
hard. Okay. Uh, space KGB agent makes a
good question. Asks good question. The
Sculp Storm Shadow missile used in war
is worth $2.5 million a piece. So, one
missile is $2.5 million. Is it worth
spending that much money for one
missile? Well, it depends on what you
use it for. If you take a $2.5 million
missile and you and you launch it at a
$100,000 drone, that is stupidity
because the drone is worth $100,000 and
the missile is 25 times more
expensive. Stupidity. But what if you
launch that $2.5 million missile at a
$100 million target or in the case of
Pakistan $10 million target because they
won't have anything worth $100
million. So it depends on what you're
using it for. You see, please
understand, every weapon in our arsenal,
in our toolkit, has a specific purpose.
We're not using $2.5 million missiles to
take out uh some some, you know,
$100,000
target. The the S400 is a very expensive
system. Do you think we use it to shoot
down those little drones coming in? No.
No. Please understand everything has its
per use and purpose and we know exactly
how to use each of these
tools. Uh Kunal Gadia says why can't we
make a steel border with Pakistan and
permanently seated just like the US
Mexico border same with Bangladesh
border.
Look the territory the terrain is very
difficult. If you look at the India
Pakistan terrain some of it is like pure
desert some of it is different kinds of
things. And when it comes to PK, why
should we build a a wall between us and
our own territory? And anyway, Pakistan
is a temporary nation in the future it
breaks up. Then we'll have to dismantle
the wall because of what whatever
reasons. It doesn't make sense. Doesn't
make sense. And it's it's super
expensive. And if you're trying to build
a wall, you think the Pakistanis will
sit and let us do it. They'll they'll
they'll create some mischief like the
ceasefire violations are happening, that
sort of thing. So it's not practical or
feasible.
Um, Tanmay says, "Do you think things
would have been different if Joe Biden
was president or it would have been much
worse for us?" It would have been much
worse for us. He would have taken
Pakistan side from the day one and he
may have even imposed sanctions on India
from day one. He may even have sent
reinforcements to, you know, not
reinforcements but uh supplies and
whatnot to Pakistan. It's possible. Joe
Biden and and Kamala Kamala Harris. Oh
god, I've not thought of her for a
while. Yeah, they were virolently
anti-India.
Okay. Karan Singh says, "Why is the
international media so biased against
India in its narrative?" It's it's a lot
of reasons, historical reasons. The West
sees India as the enemy. The West
doesn't want to see India rise. The West
says, "How dare you still stand on your
own feet and try try to become a great
nation after 250 years of British
occupation? How dare you? How dare you
still have your own culture and
civilization? How dare you not have
converted to what we have wanted to
convert to?" and how dare you be
independent, how dare you not become our
vasal and so many other things. So they
are super biased against us. That's
that's how it is.
Um okay, Dash says, can you do some
analysis about Kirana Hills strike from
the video? Look, I am not u an expert in
geoloccation and all those little
details and all that. So I can speak
about it from a distance from a from
from a larger perspective. Okay. Uh I
I'm I'm not somebody who's well versed
in those angles of attack and which
direction the thing came from and let's
take a look at the the pictures and
videos that we have and let's analyze
this trail and that that's not what I am
uh an expert in. Uh what I can say is
that I discussed this yesterday as well.
Kirana Hills is uh about 100 something
kilometers from the border. It's between
it's it's it's in Pakistani Punjab about
100 something kilometers from Amritsa
roughly right and it's a location where
the Pakistanis have stored have have
it's an underground location deep inside
a hill with the which is a Pakistani
nuclear warhead storage site so the
Pakistanis may have been thinking that
it's completely secret but we showed
them it's not secret at all and uh we
kind of scored a very direct hit at
perhaps the entrance of the tunnel so it
was a message to Pakistan. Uh that's
what I can say. I'll not analyze in
further detail.
Now, Subit Morer says, "Was this a
perfect time to use the the aircraft?
Even if it turned out not so great, we
would have got we would have still got a
lot of information and scope of
improvements from a battle tested
aircraft." I can't speculate about that.
I am not uh the aircraft is is quite
different and it has a different very
specific role. It's uh it doesn't have
long legs. Uh, it doesn't have long legs
like the Sukoy 30. The Sukoy 30 has
super long legs. What it means, it has
got very long endurance. The fuel tanks
will hold fuel for, I don't know, 2,000
3,000 km perhaps, whatever it is, very
long legs. They just has shorter legs.
So, it has it is used for a different
role. Every aircraft has a certain role
to play. Now, I'm not sure what
specificities of the battle plans were
when it comes to this current uh the
past this this recently paused 3-day
war, but obviously the air force decided
that we wanted to use certain aircraft.
Now, I'm not sure which aircraft have
been used. There's all kinds of
speculations on social media and the
official the the legacy media. But have
you seen any statement from the
government or the uh military or the or
the air force that we used so and so
kind of aircraft that we used
hypothetically the Sukoy 30 or
hypothetically the Mirage 3 2000 or
hypothetically the Rafal or whatever
else. They have made no official
statements of any kind. So who knows
maybe they just was used and they've not
spoken about it. We don't know right? We
don't know. So let's not start assuming
things. People are assuming all kinds of
things. All kinds of speculations are
flowing on on in the media. They have no
evidence to back it up.
So
okay. Uh Pratam Agaral says, "What are
what are my thoughts on India
fasttracking surveillance based
satellites program the SBS program after
the operation Synindur from four to 5
years to 12 to 18 months? What is SBS
and what are the future benefits?
I have no idea about what uh the the the
satellites do because I have no access
to this information. Obviously, I am a
le a civilian like everybody else. But
let's let's discuss what surveillance
satellites do. What's a surveillance
satellite? Uh there are so surveillance
satellites are eyes in the sky.
uh they have capabilities like they can
track what's happening geographically in
in a certain area okay they can peer
through clouds let's say even if it's
cloudy if it's the Indian rainy season
they can peer through the clouds and see
what's happening on the ground they have
such capabilities okay and uh they can
see things in various wavelengths the
vis the
the human eyes wavelength visible
wavelength the that that spectrum
They can see through things in other
wavelengths also which are not visible
to the human eye in various bands and
frequencies and all that. And they can
have very sharp resolution like you know
from from space 200 300 km above the
surface. They may be able to pick up
something the size of a cell phone
perhaps. So you can really uh keep an
eye on what's happening and they can
possibly track troop movements. they can
track possibly the movement of specific
individuals all of that in real time and
uh that sort of thing. So typically
these these are called spy satellites.
Historically in the 20th century they
were called spy satellites. Now spy
satellites typically are low earth orbit
satellites. Typically okay not always
they can always have exceptions. I'm
just saying generally. So generally a
spy satellite may hypothetically be at
an altitude of 200 300 km above the
surface of the earth. And because of
that they because they are not
geostationary. So they will just pass
through an area over and over again once
every 90 minutes or so. So it makes
makes sense to have multiple satellites.
So every time a satellite goes over a
location it doesn't go blank for 90
minutes. Soon you should have another
satellite coming in. So that's sort of
the capability you you want to have. I'm
just saying this generally. I'm not
saying we have exactly what I'm
discussing here. What India the
capabilities India has are classified.
So that's the kind of thing a
surveillance-based satellite is like and
that's the kind of thing it does and it
may do other things also. It may track
you know the American VA satellites from
the 1970s or 60s or whatever it was they
had a very very very specific function.
They their function was to uh look for
double flashes on the surface of the
planet. Double flashes. What's a double
flash? It's an initial very brief flash
and then a slow greater flash. That's
the signature of an atmospheric nuclear
weapons test and they ended up detecting
gammaray bursts which is an
astrophysical phenomenon that is a very
um well it's something that's very much
an area of interest today in
astrophysics but we talking about
something else here. So satellites have
different purposes and they have all
kinds of capabilities. um they can
detect gamma rays. They can detect uh
gamma rays are just light in a different
uh frequency and so on. So that's what
uh surveillance based satellites do.
They are essentially eyes in the sky.
They are spy satellites and they have
different purposes. So if we are
fasttracking it, it's fantastic. We need
more eyes in the sky to cover different
parts of our ge geographical uh
neighborhood. Not just west, also east,
also north, also the Indian Ocean
region. We'll have maritime based
satellites, you know, n satellites
dedicated to the needs and requirements
of the Indian Navy. They will have some
satellites dedicated to the needs and
requirements of the Indian Air Force,
the Indian armed forces and so on and so
forth. Yeah. So that's what SBS
satellites do and uh it's it's
interesting that we are now fasttracking
the program which is good. We need to
fasttrack a lot of a lot of things.
Okay. Uh, Bot Gaming says, "Pakistan uh,
developed the nuclear program and
capabilities with the help of the West
and China. Wouldn't it be foolish to
assume that they don't have plans
uh to be implemented if Pakistan goes
against them with nuclear weapons? The
Pakistani nuclear program is only and
only aimed at India. It has it is never
going to be aimed at the West. The
Pakistanis don't even have the
capability to target the west with the
nuclear weapons because their missiles
are all India specific missiles with a
range that could target India and
possibly Ian and that's more or less
like it. What's the point of targeting
Central Asia or the Gulf region? No
point, right? It's all about India. Now
the West, now the Americans, forget
about the West. The Americans will have
a very specific set of contingency plans
over Pakistan's nukes. So it's called
the worst case scenario planning. What
if Pakistan disintegrates and the
nuclear weapons start floating around
and they some of them fall into the
hands of the the Hik Taliban Pakistan.
Some fall in the hands of the Baljasthan
liberation army. Some fall in the hands
of the ISIS and some fall in the hands
of al-Qaeda and
someh whatever the hell and something
whatever these terrorist groups are
named right uh Lashkar something and so
on. So that's that's a nightmare
scenario. If nukes start floating around
like this and in the in the hands of the
worst possible individuals, human beings
on the planet of the earth on the
surface of the planet. So the Americans
will have something called a worst case
scenario. If something like this is
happening, they will swoop in and they
will uh salvage the nuclear weapons.
That's going to be the plan. So yeah,
they have these contingency plans, the
worst case scenario plans for sure. They
don't discuss these things. They don't
talk about it, but it's there.
Okay, Laki Singh says sees fire
violations in the sambar sector. Very
nice. Pakistan I think the Pakistanis
are asking for
it. Krishna says will Trump not take it
to the ego after Pakistani U-turn on
ceasefire which Pakistanis have
literally begged for. I think you know
the Pakistanis are playing true to their
nature true to form right and if
something happens then they will blame
India. So I think right now it's for
India to somehow hold the line or if if
India chooses then we can simply blame
Pakistan and let them have it I suppose.
Uh yeah so it's for our leadership to
decide how to go about uh dealing with
Pakistan's provocations and once again
Spandan says ceasefire
violated right okay what to do um
Rangers Wolf says while Russia is
focused on its own priorities how do you
think it Russia views the IndiaPakistan
war conflict and Russia's relationship
with
Pakistan see All geopolitical
relationships are based on
self-interest, national interest. There
was a time when the Russians were kind
of cozying up to Pakistan in the 2010s
in the second half of of the
2010s. Um so I think around 2015 2016
around that time the Russians and
Pakistanis started this yearly military
exercise joint military exercises called
the DRJBA exercises. DJBA means
friendship in Russian. So they called
their military exercises friendship
exercises and they were being held once
a year all the way until
2021. What happened in 2022? I wonder
the exercises stopped. Yeah. Because of
geopolitical expediency because the
Russians needed India on their side or
at least to be neutral after the uh
special military operation against
Ukraine was was was implemented. You see
how it goes? So they were trying to make
friends with Pakistan. They even sold
Pakistan some some some equipment you
know helicopters military helicopters
and such like right. So understand that
if you are strong, if you are powerful,
if you are of of if you are valuable, if
you are of some good use, then everybody
will want to be your friend. But if you
are if you are perceived to be weak and
not worth not not very valuable then
even your old friends may turn away and
seek new
friends. So that's the historical uh
that's a history lesson visav question.
Now Russia currently has its own
priorities. It is embroiled in this
never-ending war with Ukraine. Right?
Trump wanted to end it didn't work. uh
initially Trump and Putin tried to end
it but the the European nations come in
came in the way and now Trump seems to
have tired of whatever is happening and
he's no longer interested in negotiating
a ceasefire or or helping to negotiate a
ceasefire he's now interested in
Ukraine's mineral wealth the minerals
deal that he has he has had Zalinsky
sign with him right so Russia has this
ongoing war this slow war scenario long
war scenario that's unfolding on its
western southwestern frontier the
Ukraine region right and Russia because
of this has faced a lot of difficulties
they have been able to uh to withstand
the the economic siege warfare the
Americans have unleashed on them which
is called sanctions and because of that
they have been uh forced to become
overly dependent on China. So I would
not say that Russia has become a Chinese
vasal but Russia is very dependent on
China and a small number of other
nations uh for various things. So it's
China, it's North Korea, it's Iran,
that's about it, right? And India has
uh remained neutral and very autonomous
and independent in this matter and we
probably are the biggest buyer of
Russian oil right now. So we have acted
as a pressure release valve for Russia
without which they would have become an
actual Chinese vasal but in the China
Russia relationship they are kind of a
junior partner Russia. Okay. So Russia
Russia is it find itself with a
situation where it's a junior partner to
China because of China's enormous
economic clout. So that's the deal with
Russia. Now how does Russia view the
India Pakistan conflict? Russia will
want India to do well because that gives
us more leverage over Pakist. Now China
will be kind of more worried about about
India. In just 3 4 days everything has
changed. Before the India Pakistan the
the 3-day war started China would have
been very confident about potential
future military uh action against India.
Today they'll be super worried right. So
that will make Russia happy. It gives
Russia more leverage. It gives Russia
more options. But Russia is not in a
position to come and mediate or
interfere or anything. they'll sit and
look from afar and they'll be happy
about what's happened because Russia and
China they have this modus vendi right
now they have this u this this
arrangement which is not quite an
alliance but Russia and China are
long-term natural adversaries
so right HKumar says all the damage done
to Pakistan won't they recover from it
within months using loan money was this
really our objective I feel we weren't
able to achieve what we truly intended.
Look, when it comes to Pakistan, the
objective for India is to balconize
Pakistan. It's to end the threat of the
military ISI terrorism complex, the the
one unified entity which has multiple
faces military, ISI and terrorists. It's
the same thing. So our objective
obviously naturally the natural
objective is to end that. It's to
destroy that completely.
The objective for India is to once and
for all permanently end the threat that
the Pakistan terror industry poses for
India and the Pakistan terror industry
is the military industry and the ISI
industry all of that together. So we
have to dismantle Pakistan we have to
balconize Pakistan. That is the only way
that things will end for us in our in
our on our
terms and we could have been 24 to 48
hours from achieving at least the
liberation of
PK.
Yeah. Uh but Trump came in the way and
Modi is very angry about that I can tell
you. So our objective was much bigger
than this but Trump came in the way and
you can't do a thing when the Americans
come in the way. Okay. So stop crying
about this. Many Indians are very
unhappy. Come on deal with it. This is
the real world. We have to accept
certain things like
grown-ups, right? Two guys are fighting.
I'm I'm defeating my my enemy, but but a
28t guy comes in the way. Then what will
I do? Can't do a thing about it. I'm
only 6 feet. He's 28 ft tall. The other
guy was 2T tall. So I could have bashed
him up. And so that's that's the kind of
thing. Uh so the all this damage that
has been done to Pakistan, they will
buy, beg, borrow, steal whatever they
can and they will repair the damage.
they will recover from it within 6
months. The runways they will repair
them in the next uh I don't know week 2
weeks. Uh the aircraft they will have
lost uh that will be much harder to
replace those. The nuclear warheads they
may or may not have uh lost that will be
very hard to replace. But whatever they
can recover they will recover using loan
money, begging money, whatever. And
probably within 6 months they'll be back
to square back to where where we were.
and they may then restart their
terrorist misadventures possibly even
before that who knows but this time it's
going to be
different this time if they indulge in
terrorism they're going to pay a very
very heavy price and this time probably
even Trump will not be able to come in
the way so yeah uhar says should bat
join GCAP sixth generation fighter jet
program with Italy Japan and England
should India join this if India joins
what are the implications for India and
US as Japan is US facad. If you join
this then you are essentially be going
to be compromised if you use that
technology because that technology will
be um there's going to be closes in that
technology and so on that you have to
sign first of all to participate and all
of that will be essentially pro- US. Uh
so if you see these sixth generation
fighter planes etc they are they they
use something called networkcentric
warfare. So these fighter planes they
have this integrated battlesnake, a
battle
space which which comes from all kinds
of sensors which all talk to each other.
So you have a floitering drone that is
talking to your fighter plane which is
talking to your radar which is talking
to something else. So it's a whole you
get this integrated uh view of the
battle space from all these signals that
are collected together and synthesized.
So the sixth generation fighter player
fighter plane if you want it to if you
want to participate in that then you
will have to buy other weapons and other
other radar systems and other other
whatnot from them and all of that the
Americans will be in a position to
surveil right and uh it will have back
doors and kill switches and whatnot. So
you're going to be compromised if you
buy this. The best thing to do is to
develop your own technology step by step
by step. Right? So we have the the
fighter plane which is what 3.5 fourth
generation whatever it is maybe fourth
generation then you you improve upon
that by building the AMCA which is a
fifth generation fighter plane then in
10 years you build a sixth generation
fighter plane because you learn the
lessons each time from whatever you're
developing that's the right way to go
about it in the meanwhile in the interim
while we don't have the fifth generation
fighter plane you buy a bunch of Rafals
or Sukoys or whatever you want whatever
is best for India depending on what the
experts decide is best for us that's how
you do it you should I don't think India
India should join any of these coll
collaborative programs or any such
thing. India should go its own way
independently. Yeshuan says Russia
offered joint production of the S500
system with India. Should India now use
this opportunity to completely move away
from any possibility of purchasing US
weapons? I think India should consider
this very seriously. If we are offered
joint production of the S500,
uh it should mean that we get a complete
transfer of technology right and then we
can possibly manufacture it in India and
even manufacture it for Russian
usage and the S500 will be superior even
to the Russian S400. So I think it's a
if if it's a good deal they are offering
to us with a full transfer of technology
we should very seriously consider it
very seriously.
Absolutely. Okay. Your boy Pasta says uh
ceasefire violation and drone sightings
at multiple places. Uh yeah Punjab,
Sambar, Jammu and Kashmir and whatnot.
Terrible, terrible, terrible. The
Pakistanis are asking they're asking for
another
whooping. Maybe we should give them what
they what they desire.
Right. Uh, serpent serpent blade 870
says boron possibly from Egypt. US
nuclear uh nuclear detection aircraft.
Uh, I saw wind from null school
considered nuke
reaction radiation leak locally. Also,
would it be prudent to attack ordinance
factories and naval assets? It's prudent
to to attack everything that helps the
enemy. Everything is fair game. That's
fine. Now this boron look we know that
some aircraft came from Egypt some
aircraft came from the US the aircraft
the American aircraft is associated with
uh checking for nuclear radiation leaks
and all that that we know right uh I
don't know if the aircraft that came
from Egypt contains boron I don't know
who's how do we know that did they tell
the world hey hey hey we are sending
boron to Pakistan via the US did they
say anything like that so I don't know
about the boron boron is obviously uh
used in nuclear reactors for for uh for
slowing down nuclear reactions. So yeah,
it it certainly can help in you know u
absorbing radiation and and possibly
damping radiation. So if it is true then
it's interesting. It it would indicate
that we have actually uh hit something
very sensitive but I'm not sure if we
have actual hard evidence that boron has
been flown in from Egypt.
uh they just says it's high time to
start investing more in building
in-house military equipments and drones
also start investing heavily in social
media narrative. Absolutely all these
things need to happen in parallel. We
have now seen firsthand in real time
during war during battles that our
indigenous technologies is second to
none. It's probably some of the best in
the world. the atma river technology
that we have been developing in the past
few few years and I'll tell you whatever
we have achieved all of this just
compare it with what our situation was
in 2019 like I was saying yesterday in
2019 we did not do that well during the
Balacord air strikes we did not film the
air strikes we did not film we were not
able to produce any any video evidence
like we have done this time copious
evidence right we were using MIG 31 MIG
21s one of them went down on the
Pakistani side P side right we were
outmaneuvered. We made a mistake and we
ended up shooting down one of our own
helicopters right in 2019. This time
look at India in 6 years how much has
changed in our military
capabilities. Who do you thank for that?
I thank Prime Minister Modi wouldn't
have happened under anybody else. So I
think we need to continue this. The
Atman Bharat Atman military uh program
needs to be carried forward. Now we need
to invest more money into this. I think
it's time to to double our military
budget. It's high time I think to
seriously consider doubling our military
budget or at least increasing by 50% for
the next 5 10 years. Needs to happen.
Needs to happen. Imagine what we can do
with a double budget. Imagine how much
more Atman technology we'll be able to
uh build and uh supply our armed forces
with. Yeah. So we are we I think we have
some of the best drone manufacturers in
the world. I think now in India uh
that's great. So that needs to get a
real boost, a real philillip
economically, financially, right? And
obviously we need to obviously also
invest heavily in in our uh soft soft
hard power which is the social media
narrative propaganda uh capabilities.
Looks like we are not very good at that
right now and it's very clear that we
are not. So that also needs to happen.
Yes. So I completely agree with what the
is saying over here.
Um okay, Anand says, "Didn't Modi just
say we would have had complete control
over any terrorist camp in Poke
Pakistan? If Pakistan doesn't want this,
then they have to dispose of it. That
does that just mean that India is just
cleaning P now?
I Okay, I'm not sure if that was the
implication of what Prime Minister Modi
was saying. What Mr. Modi says said is
that we destroyed a whole lot of
terrorist camps and uh if Pakistan
continues terrorism then we will destroy
everything else as well. That's
essentially what Prime Minister Modi
said. Uh and he said that uh if we talk
to Pakistan we will talk only about
terrorism and P nothing else is to be
spoken about. There's no other item on
the agenda if we ever have talks with
Pakistan. That's what he said. I'm not
sure about leading P or any such thing
right now. He made it very clear to
Pakistan any any future or further
terrorist activity is going to invite
very very heavy and painful action from
India. Okay.
Um we'll not discuss uh the economy
right now but we'll discuss the India
Pakistan matter. Rurag says live drone
attack again any look I am not watching
the news so I cannot confirm anything
but uh you guys need to tell me what's
happening because I'm right now focusing
on your questions I'm not multitasking
by I don't have a command center here
with like 28 different ski screens and
I'm looking at them all okay here there
are drone sightings here there is
suicide violation no I'm looking here so
I don't know if there's confirmation you
guys let me know and I will react to
that if required
um dham
G edits says got information right now
from inside Pakistan. The drones are
still coming in from flights via Turkey
and indirect routes. Pakistanis are
using all that on us. Yes, that's that's
our good friends the Turks. When the
Turks when there were earthquakes,
devastating earthquakes in Turkey, we
sent from the goodness of our heart, we
sent rescuers, we sent equipment, we
sent medicines, we sent our our NDRF,
national disaster thing teams, we sent
doctors to help the people of Turkey
free of cost, right? We did that for
Turkey out of the goodness of our heart.
And how does Turkey repairs? by
supplying Pakistan with deadly weapons
to be used against India. So please my
friends boycott
Turkey. Boycott Turkey. Boycott
Azarbaijan. Boycott these two terrorist
friendly
nations. Boycott them. You want to go on
holiday, go to Greece. If you want to
see the Mediterranean coast, go to
Greece. Go to Italy.
Go to
Kefalonia. Go to uh the Greek islands,
the Asian sea islands, the Ionian sea
islands. Go to
Sardinia. Go to these nations. Do not
visit Turkey. Do not waste your
hardearned money on a nation that
supports your enemy. Do not visit
Azarbaijan. There are other places that
you can visit. If you want
recommendations, I'll give you
recommendations. So, yeah, that's what
we need to do.
Suraj says, "Won't Trump again threaten
us with trade in future if Pakistan
pests India? Can Trump interfere in our
discussions on P with Pakistan? How to
overcome this?" So the next time we
decide to take military action, we need
to do it very rapidly, lightning strikes
and inflict much worse damage than we've
done this time. So it's going to take
some time for them to reactivate their
air defenses. And anyway, the air
defenses don't work. So yeah, it's going
to be it's going to be difficult to some
extent if we take our time in
retaliating to what whatever Pakistan
does in the future. It should be
decisive. It should be very rapid. It
should be crippling. It's Pakistan was
already crippled right now. They have no
air defenses. They're still helpless
right now. We can just fly over Pakistan
and they can they will not be able to
hit you. So yeah, we'll have to do that
again, I
suppose. Uh Krishna says, "Today's army
briefing was quite chilled out. I didn't
see the didn't get the reason why it was
held. They didn't provide much details
any reason for holding it. Uh I did not
watch it but there must be some good
reason for holding it. It's not about uh
like what we have on India's TV networks
that we have to shout and do all that.
There are good reasons for doing all
these things. It's about putting things
on the record and so on. So yeah, I'm
sure there was a good reason for
it. Uh I will not take questions about
religion etc. That's not what I do. So
please don't ask that. Please ask better
questions. Questions pertinent to the
situation. Uh Nikl says why did Modi G
agree to ceasefire on what conditions?
What are some points according to you
that Modi G knew but are not in the
public domain? If there is something
that Modi G knows and it is not in the
public domain, I am not supposed to
discuss it. And secondly, I don't know
what Modi G knows which is not in the
public domain. So I can discuss what is
there in the public domain and analyze
the situation and draw inferences for
it. Right? Okay. Once again this
question by Sush was this a perfect
question to use a theious aircraft even
if it turned out not so great we still
would have still got a lot of
information and scope of improve
improvements from a battle tested
aircraft. Now once again let me
reiterate we don't know which aircraft
we used. Maybe the tis was used. I don't
know. Right? We don't know. You have all
these YouTubers and social media
channels and media channels who are
speculating
wildly without having any actual
information. The government of India,
the army, the air force have not put out
any statement about which aircraft were
involved in the operation. So why are we
speculating what was used, what was not
used? How do you know? How do these
media channels know what was used or
what was not
used? Let's not speculate like that. So
maybe it was used and maybe we have some
information.
Um okay what are the
questions? Uh 180 days transformation
that's a good thing 6 months
transformation. Uh do you think India's
action of often banning world media like
BBC Alazer could be one of the reasons
why the world media is portraying India
as bad? No it's the other way around. We
have to sometimes block these channels
because of their attitude towards India.
It's not the other way around. It is
this way
around.
Okay.
Um Di Chri says, "Is there a possibility
of India using ASAT weapons against
Pakistan?" Now, that's an interesting
question. Does Pakistan have spy
satellites? Does Pakistan have these
deep surveillance satellites positioned
over Indian
territory? If such satellites do use do
exist then it could make sense for us to
use our ASAT weapon and blow those
satellites to
bits but I don't think Pakistan has
those capabilities so so it doesn't make
sense to use those right now the ASAT
weapon can be used for other purposes
also like destroying an an incoming
ballistic missile so in that case you
could perhaps use the kill vehicle of
the ASAT weapon
for that purpose. But the Pakistanis
don't have any uh such satellites that
they can use to spy upon India. That's
why we haven't used them. Now, Theodore
says, "Why aren't we retaliating to the
drone attacks?" Uh I think that's a
question for the government to answer. I
don't know. I'm not sure what's
happening right now. It looks like the
Pakistanis are are are violating the
ceasefire over and over again in small
ways, but we'll see.
Uh, Chirang Shetty says, "Do you think
our prime minister's speech humiliated
or angered Aim Munir, hence the drone
attack? Now, will Aim Munir have
Hitler's downfall this time?" Uh, I
don't care whether it angered the fellow
or whatever or it humiliated him.
Pakistan is humiliated. Pakistan is on
its knees with its pants down
essentially. Right. Right now, they are
helpless. They are defenseless. They
have no air defenses.
their runways are cratered. They can't
even have their fighter planes take off
or land over there. They are completely
exposed. I know they are totally
humiliated. Um and if the prime
minister's speech humiliated them
further, so be it. Of course, it was
humiliating to rub it in their faces,
right? And maybe that's why the drone
attacks are happening right now. If uh
the drone attacks cross a certain limit,
I'm sure we're going to retaliate again.
Will Asimir have Hitler's downfall this
time? Let the gods decide. Let the gods
decide what happens to Aim Moner. The
thing is, look, why are we obsessing
about
Aim? Let's say he he's he has a
downfall. Then somebody else will come
in his place who will be as bad as
him. Another terrorist will come will
take his place. What difference does it
make to you? Whether it is Aim Mun or or
whoever else at the head of the
Pakistani terror machine, what
difference does it make to you? Makes no
difference. The only way it will make a
difference is they're if they're all
eliminated, right?
Um, okay. Uh, c dun I don't know what
dun is, but ceasefire bio
relation. What's a ceasefire bio?
Cheese. What's a cheesefire bio
relation? I've never seen that term in
my entire life. I've seen a lot of
things in my life.
Cheesefire
bioreation. I commend you sir or ma'am
whoever you are. Cheesefire bore
relation. Um Nishan Singh says why
doesn't India support the Kurds at the
UN and support Greece openly? There are
good reasons for that. There are look at
this time we are not that that big a
power that we can go around pushing
everybody else around and throwing our
weight around. Let's mind our business.
Look at where our national interest is.
and focus only on that. That's what we
need to do. I know it is part of our
peripheral interests, you know. Yeah,
that that's this is the problem because
nobody teaches the national interest in
school, college, university. So, you
have no idea. There are various there's
a set of national interests. There are
national interests come in various
different categories.
There's something called core interests
or critical interests. Vital interests.
Core/critical/vital. Let's call them
vital interests. Those are
non-negotiable
interests. That's one category of
national interests. Then there are
important interests that are slightly
less vital than the vital interests, but
they're still quite important. And then
there are peripheral interests, but
they're all interrelated. So the
question of the Kurds and the Greece
etc. that's kind of more peripheral than
vital. Greece may be more important and
not so peripheral but definitely not
vital. So that's how it goes. We have to
classify and categorize things
properly. Uh util card says can Pakistan
come with better air defense system
after some years and attack India again?
If so what should be India strategy? A
good question. It depends on who's going
to supply these systems to the
Pakistanis. The Chinese have supplied
their best system to the Pakistanis
apparently as far as I can tell and
those systems have failed. Then who else
can supply Pakistan with better air
defense system systems? Will the
Russians do it? I don't think the
Russians will do it. Doesn't make sense
for them to do it. Will the French do
it? No way. No way. Will the Americans
do it? Now that's a question mark. Yeah,
that's a question mark.
So yeah, if it if the Americans supply
them with better air defense system or
if the Chinese improve their air defense
systems and supply them to Pakistan
after let's say 6 months, one year, then
we will have a different set of troubles
on our border. Then the Pakistan may
Pakistanis may decide to attack India
again. So we need to keep an eye on
what's happening in Pakistan. We need to
have our intelligence
operations on top of their game. We need
to be know we need to know exactly
what's happening in inside Pakistan in
real time. We need to have intelligence
assets within
Pakistan. So we need to do all this and
whatever developments happen we need to
be prepared for them. So it's a cat and
mouse game. It's a cat-and- mouse game.
It's an ongoing neverending
game. Rashmi says Modi has said that if
there are any talks with Pakistan there
will either be about Pakistan or Kashmir
or terrorism. Did he say this indirectly
in response to Trump's offer to mediate
on the Kashmir issue? I think it was not
indirect. It was pretty
direct. Right. Trump has made the claim
via his minion Marco Rubio that India
and Pakistan have decided have agreed
have agreed that they will hold talks at
some neutral venue or something like
that. said. So this is a refutation of
the American
claim that if we do talk at some point
in time with the Pakistanis, the talks
will be about Pakistan occupied Kashmir
and they'll be about terrorism, nothing
else. So this is a reputation of what
the Americans are
saying. Yeah. So Trump needs to, you
know, take it easy. This is none of your
business. If you make it your business,
then it's not going to then you're going
to have problems in your relationship
with
us. Uh
okay. Geopolitical Dub Dubet says there
are reports that Gagyan mission is
delayed again. Okay. I'm not aware of
that but we will see. We'll see about
that. I I'll check it out. This is
something that that definitely interests
me as you I'm sure you know. So, thank
you for letting me know. I'll check it
out.
Um Singh says on the one hand sir you
say that the Indian defense system is
the best in the world. On the other you
say the Indian forces cannot be compared
to even 2000 the the American um forces
of the of the 2000s. Aren't these
completely
contradictory? You have to understand
nuance. Viv when I was talking about the
2000s America, I was talking about the
overall hard power which is associated
with the the US military and the Indian
military which is essentially military
offensive capability and power
protection capability.
Right? When it comes to the Americans
and their air defense system, they have
the Patriot system. They also have the
Aegis system that is used to uh that's a
point defense system used for warships.
So the uh whenever there's a US uh
aircraft carrier task force battle group
that goes out somewhere they there's a
aircraft carrier and there's about 10
more at least 10 more battleships which
form a defensive ring around the
aircraft carrier with the Aegis system.
Now, the Aegis system, I'm not sure if
it's ever been battle
tested. Battle tested. It's tested in
during the manufacturing and approvals
process. Sure. But has it ever been
battle tested in real combat when
there's incoming fire at you? It's not
been tested. The Patriot system, it was
battle tested once or twice here and
there. It's never taken the it's never
faced the the quantum of incoming fire
like we like the Akash and other systems
faced in the last three days the
three-day
war. So what I said is that the Indian
air defense system is the world's best
battle tested system today and I stand
by what I'm saying. I'm talking about
one component of the Indian
capabilities. I'm not talking about the
overall Indian capabilities. Please
learn to appreciate some nuance.
It's not contradictory whatsoever.
Please, please learn. Please learn. I
want Indians to understand things
better. It's important that we
understand nuance and small subtleties
in
things. What can I
say?
Okay. Um, let's take more questions. Uh,
Sibin Raj SB says, "How can we tackle
America's tariff blackmail in the
future? because India seems to climb the
escal escalation slowly after Pakistan
attack. Uh is there any other
possibility? No, you can at this point
in time India can do absolutely nothing
to counter Trump's tariff blackmail.
Take it deal with
it. We are 6 feet tall. The Pakistanis
are 2t tall. The United States is 28t
tall.
Look at it from that perspective because
nuance doesn't seem to be a forte here.
There's nothing we can do for the next
20 30 years about this. Deal with that.
So if this hurts you then work as hard
as you possibly can. All of us we work
as hard as we possibly can to change the
situation. Do you understand? This is
what is coming in our
way. If we had started this process of
atmana and what not in 1947 do you think
Trump would come in our way
today? So you see the process started
only recently the last 10 years or
so which is why we are seeing rapid
progress. We are no longer the India of
2019. We are today's India 2025 which is
a whole different beast. Imagine where
we will be in 2030. So we have to keep
up this rate of progress. Today there is
nothing we can do to counter Trump's
tariff and trade blackmail. Absolutely
nothing. We have to swallow it and we
have to bide our time. That's the deal.
That is the
deal. Rahul says we won. Yes, we won.
And this was way larger than Cargill. No
question about it. This
was orders of magnitude lar larger than
Cargill in Cargill. Okay, let's look at
the map. We Let's Let's look at the map,
right? Because that's the right way of
understanding what Rahul is is pointing
out. Where is Cargill? Let's let's
search for
Cargill. Cargill. Cargill. So, here we
go in. So Cargill is this small
location, small geographical location
where you have Tiger Hill and whatnot.
Okay, let's uh yeah, there we have it.
So it's a small geographical
location. Of course, we can zoom out and
see it bigger. So that's where the
Pakistanis had in the winter of what 98
99 whichever year it was they had taken
over stealthily some Indian territories
and positions and in this small little
location
u we had defeated them after a lot of
fighting. So that was the cargill war.
Now in 2025 the three-day war we have
struck Pakistan everywhere deep inside
Pakistani
territory I don't have the list of uh
military installations and terror camps
and air force bases and whatever else we
have targeted we have hit them
everywhere we have hit them at will
we've hit them deep inside Pakistan we
have hit them in the heart of the
military ISI terrorism complex in Rahul
Pindi we have hit Nurh Khan air base
we've destroyed Saroda we've hit
everything we've given all the evidence
anybody can want about us hitting them.
This is way way way larger than Cargill.
This is Cargill was nothing compared to
this. Nothing to I'm not trying to take
away uh anything from the bravery of our
soldiers who fought the Cargill war. But
our capabilities at the time were very
different and very limited. Very limited
compared to what we have
today. So you see with economic growth
comes military growth and with military
growth comes the kind of result we have
seen today.
Right? That needs to continue. So we
what we have achieved is probably the
biggest victory since 1971. But there
has been no change of the lines on the
map. That's the one missing element in
terms of destruction to Pakistan. It was
way larger than Kaggle. Yes. But
Pakistan being Pakistan, they're still
spreading the lies that they won. We
need to up our PR game PR game. I agree
with that. I agree. Absolutely.
We need to up our PR
game. Now, Akshit says, "Do you think
China is unhappy about America's
mediation? China is behind the ceasefire
violations." I think China is actually
happy this stopped. Uh they're not
unhappy with us with America's
mediation. If America had not mediated
today, we would be probably in P and
much more. By now, Pakistan would be
would have been would have collapsed
probably. So, that would be bad for
China also. They also have some use for
Pakistan.
So China is not happy unhappy about the
American mediation about Trump coming in
the way of India's complete victory.
They'll actually be happy about it. Is
China behind the ceasefire violations? I
can't speculate about that. Who knows?
Maybe Trump is behind the ceasefire
violations. He doesn't seem to be
unhappy about the ceasefire violations.
He has not tweeted that Pakistan should
stop violating the ceasefire. So maybe
Trump is behind the ceasefire
violations. I can speculate that way
also.
Right. Uh Daran Sha says, "What do you
make of these minor drone incursions
daily? Is it the
reconnaissance?" I don't know. It could
be it could be just
uh it it could be the Pakistan is trying
to spite India. It could be the Pakistan
is trying to taunt India. It could be
the Pakistan is trying to to provoke
India into starting the war again, which
makes no sense actually at all. But then
Pakistan makes no sense actually at all.
Right? So I I'm not sure. But uh yeah,
it's strange. Paris says, "Will India
buy the S400 if Russia is offering it as
the West may object?" The West objected
to the S400. When we were purchasing the
S400, the Americans were threatening
Katza sanctions on us. We went ahead and
bought it anyway. And I'm sure it's
played a role in the three-day war. And
I'm sure it's played a significant role
possibly in the three-day war with which
which we just won. If the Russians are
offering the S500 joint production as we
hear, I think we should take it very
seriously. We should consider it very
seriously and I would actually say we
should go ahead and buy it and have the
production lines set up in India. Not
assembly lines but production lines. I
think we need to go ahead and do this
especially after Trump coming in our
way. I think we should go ahead and do
that.
Uh Priya Ranjanjan says should India
explore chances to widen the Siliguri
corridor considering the Bangladesh
China threat in the northeast. Uh I
think we should not open too many fronts
of fighting at the same time. We need to
be patient. We have so many
problems all around. We have internal
problems. 100 million Bangladeshes in
India and Rohingyas and cookies and
Pakistanis and God knows what else.
Uh so we have to take it one thing at a
time. We cannot start fighting 78
different battles at the same time.
Right? Of course, if the opportunity
does present itself on on a platter, we
should take it. I am not against that.
Right? Uh but overall, we should not
start new things right now. Let's let's
first focus on the Pakistani threat. It
still exists. Right? Uh Nikl says in the
future, if India decides to denuclearize
Pakistan, how can it be done? As we've
already hit the entrance of nuclear
facility, Kirana Hills, shouldn't we
completely take away their
blackmail? Look, the Pakistani nuclear
blackmail is over. If they
really had a plan of using nuclear
weapons against India when required,
don't you think they would have used
them in the past three days in the
three-day war? Don't you think they
would have used them? We brought them to
their knees. We were striking them at
will. In in 30 minutes we hit nine
Pakistani air bases. The jewel the crown
jewels of Pakistan. The air bases. They
had so much pride about. We hit them
over and over again. Nine air bases in
30 minutes. They were helpless. Our
aircraft were flying over over their air
bases taunting the Pakistanis. You at
that point in time if you don't use your
nuclear weapons you're never going to
use your nuclear weapons. The Pakistani
military blackmail is gone. But of
course the question remains about the
Pakistani nuclear warheads. Right? So I
don't know what the plans are. I am sure
we have plans. I'm sure we have
contingency plans. Uh we need to have
plans or military needs to have plans
and I'm sure we have them. The plans
should be to how to secure the nukes
very rapidly. If Pakistan is breaking up
or something and I'm sure we have plans
in place for that and I will not discuss
them because I'm not aware of them. But
let us trust our armed forces. As you
can see, they are super professional,
super competent, probably the best armed
forces in the world. So, let's trust
them. I'm sure they have the plans in
place.
Okay.
Um, Ishika says, "Trump gave tariff
relaxation to China and China did the
same. Is this connected to the three-day
war?" I cannot answer this question at
this point in time because I haven't
studied this tariff. relaxation that's
happened apparently quite recently. I
haven't studied that yet. I've been
focusing on the India Pakistan issue the
past few days. So I haven't studied this
in detail. I'll have to go ahead and
take a look at that and uh yeah then
maybe I'll be able to connect the dots.
I'm sure everything is to a larger or
smaller extent interconnected. So what
are the connections? I'm not quite sure
but yeah it's something I'll keep in
mind and maybe next time we can discuss
that.
Um okay Jatirya says I was watching Safh
electronics YouTube in which in one of
the videos they were saying that they
are using a thousand-year-old wax
molding technique to build blades of the
engine B- roll was Indian D statue okay
okay interesting interesting for sure
uh Motrika says China recently tested a
hydrogen non-uclear bomb can this be a
threat to us I suppose Anything can be a
threat to us. Any weapon can be used in
various contexts. So it can be a threat
to us for sure. Yes. I am I've not seen
the details of this test. I've heard of
it vaguely. It's a hydrogen-based bomb
apparently, but it's a non-uclear bomb.
So you know there's a nuclear bomb
that's called the hydrogen bomb. It's
actually a fish and fusion fish and
fusion thermonuclear bomb. It's got an
initial fishision reaction that g that
then triggers a secondary fusion
reaction and the fusion reaction has way
more energetic output than the fish
reaction. It's a two-stage process
roughly speaking fish then fusion
thermonuclear bomb and it's all it was
called the hydrogen bomb in the 20th
century. Dave Kver says drones are being
cited in Jalander, Punjab and Jammu. Why
is Pakistan violating the ceasefire? Are
they out of their sane minds? I Pakistan
are crazy. They're crazy. I I don't know
how much we will tolerate this. Maybe we
should just restart. We should restart.
Tina Yadav says red card penalty etc.
Why is Trump silent on the violation of
the ceasefire? Why can't he take credit
of that? Hate
him. Yeah, I I don't think Trump has a
lot of uh love or respect in India right
now. and what he has done I think it
will never be
forgotten and right now the Pakistanis
are violating the ceasefire and Trump
seems to be perfectly fine with that. So
yep like they say in
Hindi. Okay. Anand says
India K against the US. I'm not sure
what you're saying, sir, but I have
taken note of what you said. I tried.
Sorry. I'm so sorry. Please make it more
clear then I'll understand. Thank you.
My fault. My fault that I could not
understand. Um, Mlevin says, "Do you
think we beat Pakistan too hard and fast
which make which made others look bad?
Could we have taken the Russian
approach?" No. Doesn't make sense to
take the Russian slow war approach, long
war approach that they are doing in
Ukraine. Completely different context,
completely different situation. In the
case of Pakistan, we need to have a
pulse pose
war, very rapid advance, take territory,
then stop unilaterally as per our
convenience. Before that, obviously, we
would take out the air defenses, air
force, all all that stuff. So it was
already done. The situation was
perfectly ripe for the next phase which
was the pulse pose war which is taking
back P. It has to be done very rapidly.
Don't take don't give the chance to the
enemy. Don't give your enemy the chance
to recuperate or get reinforcements. So
our scenario is very different from the
Russian
scenario. Uh SN says Pakistan did drone
attack again in Samba Jammu Kashmir
after honorable prime minister's address
to the nation.
I think they they are really really uh
testing our patience and asking for it.
I think India should perhaps go ahead
and restart operation
sindur. Duchma says keeping the history
of the temporary nation in mind. It's
clear that the ceasefire is not for
peace but because their nuclear sites
were hit. Do you think do you think the
ceasefire is because they tried to push
a red button? I don't think they tried
to push a red button. Maybe they
threatened to Trump that we will push
the red button. But if they should have
pushed it, they should have pushed it
long ago. We brought them completely to
to a state of utter helplessness. If you
still don't push the red button, you're
never going to push the red button. Uh
so the ceasefire is not for peace. It's
because they they the ceasefire is
because the Americans inter interfered.
The Americans intervened.
See there is speculation that we hit
some nuclear storage sites which is uh
sites where the Pakistanis had stored
nuclear weapons. So it's possible we hit
those. Uh we know that Nurhan most
likely has nuclear warheads stored.
Nurhan air base and we hit that very
hard. Saroda possibly they have nuclear
weapons there possibly. And the Kirana
Hills storehouse there's a bunk set of
bunkers in in deep inside a hill. We hit
that. So it looks like we may have hit
their nuclear storage sites and some
warheads may have been destroyed. Very
possible. But there's another angle to
this. We hit nine Pakistani air bases.
The the the crown jewels of Pakistan. We
hit nine air bases in about 30 minutes.
Right? Some of these air bases obviously
will have
F-16s. That's an American fighter plane.
Now the
Americans they
have technical and other
personnel in
place in whatever air base houses
F-16s. So wherever you have F-16s in a
Pakistani air base there is a set of
American personnel over there who
babysit the F-16s 24 by7. They never let
the F-16s out of their sight.
So if we hit air bases where American
technical personnel and other personnel
are
there, what did we
hit? Maybe possibly
perhaps that's why the Americans came in
the way. You know there are things that
uh there are multiple reasons why this
could have happened.
Um now, uh Ashish says, "Why are they
sending drones now? Please make it make
sense. Let's assume they're not stupid."
Okay, that that's that's another
perspective we should take seriously.
Let's assume the Pakistan is not are not
stupid. What's their plan? Is it to drop
weapons for terrorists?
Uh that could be one plan. But maybe the
terrorists have been neutralized when
the warfare is happening. We could we
can do whatever we want. Maybe maybe
it's not to drop weapons for terrorists.
Is it for doing recognizance? I think
recognizance is not needed. They know
exactly what's happening on India's
side, right? Maps are available.
Satellite imagery is available.
Everybody has the commercial commercial
satellite imageries available which is
pretty detailed and um the past during
the three-day war they sent hundreds of
drones. Uh so reconnaissance would have
been done. The drones not only you are
used to drop weapons and bombs and
whatnot, but also even if it's a suicide
drone, it can collect intelligence and
do reconnaissance. So that's already
done. So why are they sending drones
now? I think they are trying to provoke
India into starting starting the war
again. And and they know that India has
committed to Trump that we will honor
honor the ceasefire. So they're taunting
us. They're provoking
us and they're trying to see how far we
will go. And if something starts again,
then maybe they can have Trump get angry
and blame India for it. Maybe that's the
kind of play they are
doing. Adicta Singh Takur says my father
in army is posted in Satwari Jammu. He
said more than 23 battalions are called
in Jammu and Kashmir. Is something big
going to happen? We'll see about that. I
cannot speculate. I cannot speculate.
Um Ichino Senpai says a former row
official said that India has destroyed
Pakistan's nuclear arsenal and all
recent earthquakes were caused by Indian
missiles started striking their nuclear
sites. What are my
thoughts? I am not a row official so I
cannot speculate further beyond what he
is
saying. Possible maybe not maybe yes
don't know.
uh there have been earthquakes recently
so it it is not impossible what you are
saying that's that's what I can say
uh Shri Ramachandraaya Namaha says why
are why do Russians sell their weapons
to China reverse engineers everything
you have no idea how much they reverse
engineered everything I have a list
somewhere of every weapon the Chinese
have reverse engineered they have
reverse engineered everything my
question is why can't We do
that. Anyway, coming back to this
question, which is a good question. Why
are the Russians still sending selling
their weapons to China? Like they have
sold the S400 to the Chinese. I can
assure you the Chinese will try and
reverse engineer that as well. See,
right now, Russia has very little
friends left. The whole of the West is
against Russia, right? And all the other
non-western nations, most of them are
are arm twisted into being away from
Russia. It's only China, Iran, North
Korea that are with Russia more or less
officially. North Korean soldiers are
fighting in the Ukraine war. Iran is
selling shahed to drones to the Russians
and China and Russia are cooperating in
a whole in a whole variety of of ways.
So these are the allies that the
Russians have. They had Syria as well,
but Assad is gone. So the West has taken
over Syria and they have placed a
professional head chopper as the
so-called president of Syria. Apart from
these countries, uh Russia has India
kind of on its side because we value our
age-old relationship, time- tested
relationship with Russia. Uh but we are
not official allies with Russia and we
are also dealing with the west in our
own way. So at this point in time, the
only major hefty nation the Russians
have on its on their side is China.
And uh because of these reasons they
have
to you know make some compromises when
it comes to China. If they had the the
the choice they would not sell these
weapons to China given the Chinese track
record of reverse engineering
everything. But right now they are in a
tight
spot. Um Om says why deny a strike on
nuclear facilities when the prime
minister says we are not afraid of it
because you always keep strategic
ambiguity. We always keep things
ambiguous. Why do you have to put it out
there in the public? No need for it.
That's what grown-ups
do. Uh yeah, we will not discuss
Instagram stories
today. Amisha says, "Can you explain the
role of ISRO in Operation Synindur?"
ISRO was not involved directly in
operation Synindur, but ISRO puts up the
satellites in space right in Earth
orbit. And uh the satellites some of
them are are designed and built in ISRO.
Some of them are designed and built in
various other locations and assembled
together somewhere else and ISRO does
the final assembly of the space of the
of the of the satellite within the
fairing system of the rocket and all of
that stuff. So the
satellites our surveillance satellites
our so-called spy satellites ISRO is
very much uh connected to those either
directly or indirectly definitely
directly in the in the sense that we
ISRO has placed them in orbit. So that's
as much as I can tell you. I don't think
beyond that there was any direct other
role of ISRO in operation synindor. But
without ISRO and without this capability
of rock of of rockets that can launch
satellites and without this technical
capability of constructing extremely
uh powerful high-end satellites, we
would not be in the same position today.
U even regarding operation sindur I am
pretty sure that the that the satellite
and remote sensing capabilities played a
very big role in operation sindur but
that won't be spoken
about
okay all
right man says I listen to both press
briefings by Pakistan and India see we
Indians want to listen to everybody
before we draw draw our
conclusions we that that's the thing
about Indians that's a good thing to
have. So I am confused about who won.
They also claimed they won. They also
presented satellite pictures. They said
they targeted our S400 and destroyed the
Brahmos. See, I'll tell you something,
Arman. In case you're not a student, in
case you're a grown-up and you have your
own money and all, purchase a one month
subscription of commercial satellite
imagery. It will not be very cheap, but
it won't be super expensive. It will not
cost you an arm and a leg. So purchase a
one month subscription. You can cancel
after 1 month. Purchase a one month
subscription of any highquality
commercial satellite imagery which has
images that are refreshed every day or
every week or something. And then look
at the the latest satellite images of
all the places the Pakistanis claim to
have damaged or or hit or
destroyed. Make your own conclusions
based on what you see. I am telling you
the Pakistanis are
lying. Now fact check what I am saying.
Go ahead do this and come to your own
conclusions. I'm telling you the
Pakistanis are lying. They are making
all kinds of claims. They are using
doctorred images. They using
photoshopped images and most of the
images they have not even been able to
show. They said that they hit so many
places in India. Show us the the proof
Baba. Show us. they haven't been able to
do that. So my point is it is good to be
skeptical. It is a good practice to be
skeptical about all kinds of claims and
then you need to crossverify for
yourself. You need to do the
factchecking for yourself. Now I am
making the claim that Pakistanis are
lying and we are not and I'm telling you
how you can verify for yourself. So
please sir Arman G please go ahead and
do that. That's how we will know who's
really telling the truth and who's
really
lying. Jack Sparrow says, "How do
blackouts work?" I mean, why do we need
blackouts in cities today? The
militaries have advanced GPS systems in
current times. So, why do you need
blackouts? Why? You
see, there is something called GPS
jamming, my friends.
You need to learn about these things. If
you are interested in military matters,
there is something called GPS jamming.
You can jam the GPS of incoming drones
or missiles or whatever aircraft. You
can do that. You can jam. The the
Americans have dedicated fighter planes
with electronic warfare suites on them
which do all this jamming. It's
possible. We also may have GPS jamming
capabilities and electronic warfare
capabilities. So in case the incoming
drone is now blind, it has no access to
GPS. It will still try and strike
something, right? And then it'll maybe
it's a remote control drone with a
camera on it, then it will look for
where is the light. In that case, does
it not make sense to black everything
out. Please look think one layer deeper
than what what is apparent at first uh
at face value. And now that you're
mentioning GPS, that's an interesting
thing you've mentioned. You mentioning
GPS here, right? Interesting point that
you have brought out which has come to
my mind
now. Do you
think
our
drones, our missiles use
GPS? Do you think the Indian harup
drones, other Kami Khaza drones,
loitering munitions etc. Do you think
Indian missiles, Brahos missile and
whatever else, do you think they use GPS
technology, global positioning system
which belongs to the United States? Do
you know in the Cargill war the
Americans switched off GPS for
us and we had to rely on non-GPS means
which was nothing at all, just visual
tracking. Do you think we'll make the
same mistake again? We have our own
systems now. We don't rely on GPS. We
may have a module inside each uh missile
or drone or whatever which uses multiple
sources. GPS plus Indian plus Russian
plus whatever else plus whatever else.
I'm just I'm speculating. I'm not saying
maybe we using Russian
stuff. But we have our own satellite
constellations and all and I think those
are reliable. The Americans if they get
the chance they'll switch off GPS for
us. They may have done it. Who? Who
knows? Also, they may have switched off
GPS for us this time, but we won't we
probably won't mention it. It's a
possibility that the Americans may have
switched off GPS in the past 3 days for
our armed forces and yet it made no
difference in case it happened. So,
that's the value of having your own
technology,
right? Okay. Um
uh duch atma this is complete
speculation allegedly I don't I don't we
don't discuss allegedly here okay we
don't discuss allegedly stuff here
speculation
um nationalist says even if operation
synindur is is currently paused
militarily is there any possibility that
the operation is going on hidden from
the world inside the Pakistani
government's inner fault lines hitting
those targets needs someone
there. All possibilities are
theoretically
open and there are things that happen
behind the scenes, right? There's a
whole world of of what they call black
operations out there. Every country that
has any capabilities for this does it.
Now, we don't discuss that because we
have no no knowledge of it. But
theoretically, everything is possible
for sure. For sure.
Um
uh okay Priya Ranjan says a bit extreme
but is the best way to handle Pakistan
simply to hit back periodically under
the guise of anti-terror operations as
it's going to violate ceasefire every
time
anyways.
Um it's one way of doing things. Uh yeah
it's it's definitely one way of doing
things. The thing is that it's anyway
going to viral the ceasefire
periodically. They have a habit of doing
that. So I would say every time they vi
violate the ceasefire periodically we
get a just cause for hitting them back
right. So that they themselves are
giving us the best way to handle them.
So I would say every time they they
violate the ceasefire we should hit
them. We should hit back. And I would
also say that now is the time that every
time the Pakistanis violate the
ceasefire or try or try to target
civilians in Punch or Hajori wherever we
should start salami slicing their
territory. Take 10 meters at a time.
Take 20 m at a time. Salam is slice.
Salam is slice. Take the take the first
checkpoint, the first uh post that they
have, military post. You you go and
gobble it up. Then you defend it. Then
let's have a gunfight for a for a week.
Let's let it let it be. We know how to
fight with guns. We know how to fight
with mortars. Let's start salami slicing
Pakistani territory. I think that's what
needs to happen now. They will never
learn a lesson unless we start doing
these things.
Um all right what
else okay once again this question um
Russia has offered us joint production
of S500 at full transfer of technology
should we take it what happen then what
will then happen to project Kusha so
that's an interesting question yeah I I
definitely said that we should
definitely take the technology if they
are offering us this technology we
should take it we should do joint
production but we should not stop our
own development of a similar system So
we have this thing called uh project
Kosha or whatever the the name is and as
you can see we have a tremendously
capable air defense system already which
has lots of different components that
don't
really fit together into one integrated
package. We have the Barak system. We
have the S400 system. We have the Akash
system superstar system. We have the
Pora system which is the legacy system.
We have the L70 system which is an even
more legacy system and together these
things work brilliantly together but
they are not integrated into one
package. Now we are in the process of
developing something like the S400 which
would inre which would include all kinds
of other things as well possibly the P3
air defense system etc. So we should
continue developing that. We should also
acquire the
S500 and get full transfer of technology
which which which we can then use in the
other project the project Kusha and
perhaps enhance it. So we should
certainly do that. We should not let the
existing project
uh simply meander
away. Um McLevin says I remember that in
2022 we launched the Brahmos in Pakistan
by mistake. Was it a way to test their
air defenses? Could be but I don't know
for sure. Could be. It's possible.
Uh okay. Unshul says is there a
possibility that the Chinese may have
provided the lowest of the lowquality
radar system to the to the temporary
nation and why is India letting Starink
inside? Won't it be disastrous? So the
possibility every possibility exists but
from what I hear the Chinese had
provided the best systems to
Pakistan for defending Pakistan against
India. So yeah, so I can't speculate
about that. Why is India allowing
Starlink inside? I think we need to
reconsider that very very
seriously. We need to reconsider
Starlink very seriously. I would say we
need to
launch our own satellite constellation.
We have Jio in India, right? Reliance is
Jio. Why can't we have Geolink as a
superior competitor to Starlink? give
ISRO two years to develop more powerful
rockets that can launch a 100 geolink
satellites in one go and then create our
own constellation with better technology
than Starlink. You don't think we can
have better satellites than Starling
satellites? We certainly can. We should
become a competitor to Starling. We
should not allow Starling to beam their
satellite internet into India because
then whenever there's a riot or there's
some some kind of insurgency like the
whatever then even if you switch off the
internet in that area the the enemies of
the nation will be able to get Starling
access and we cannot I mean even if we
tell Starling to switch off the beams in
some region it's going to depend
entirely on them. So it compromises our
national security and sovereignty. So we
need to reconsider Starlink very
seriously. Very
seriously. Uh Amar Deendra DH says they
have violated the ceasefire again.
They've started attacks with drones
again. There's blackout now in Punjab
and
Rajasthan. What can I say? The
government of India needs to do
something about this. We can't just sit
and take this. We can't just sit and
take this. Okay. Mansa says, "Isn't it
better to align with China than with the
US after what Trump has done? India and
China have the world's biggest
population. We can do tra we can trade
better and push the US away." It all
depends on the
Chinese the way they behave, Chinese
behavior. The Chinese have historically
and consistently been anti-India. They
fought a war with India in 1962. They
fought which we lost. They fought a war
in 1967 which we won and no one talks
about it. They there were very serious
border clashes in Arunachal region in
1987. In 2020 they did the Dclam thing.
They have consistently been our
adversary, our enemy. They have been the
ones starting every fight and they have
consistently in the past tried to salam
slice into our territory, take bits and
pieces. It's only in the last 10 years
or so that we have finally de developed
infrastructure in the in the northern
regions so that the Chinese can no
longer salami slice us. And still they
may be trying and they support our
adversaries. They have they have
published papers and books in which
they've advocated for the disintegration
of India, the bulcanization of India.
They are currently working with Muhammad
Vinos who goes to Beijing and says that
we need to cut off India's far east,
India's northeast and and that sort of
thing. They have supplied all kinds of
weapon systems to Pakistan. They have
projects going through going on through
P. They conduct joint exercises with the
Pakistani military in Pakistan occupied
Kashmir. when the do when the the
pahelgam attack happens that's not a
friendly nation the last year or so they
have been making some overtures to India
asking for some kind of uh possible
reconciliation of
sorts and there is now less tension on
the India Tibet border and the
Kailashhatra may now resume but at the
same time they are entrrenching
themselves and and and uh and increasing
their their military entrrenchment
in the northern part of the India Tibet
border in on their occupied side. So you
know what they would love to have
friendship with China but they have a
very different approach towards India.
So it is because of them that they have
we have to uh deal with people like
Trump otherwise we would be very happy
to have the best of relations with
China. We have no cultural issues with
China. India and China were never
neighbors for 2,000 how long has China
existed? 3,000 years three and a half
thousand years. We have been such good
friends to
China and we have given them so much of
our culture and
civilization right it's their fault
they're doing this so we would love to
have that friendship back but they don't
want it so what can I say so what Mansa
is saying is right it would be great if
this happens but the Chinese don't want
this to happen so we have no choice you
see we have no
choice okay
Now our rules is why isn't India
stopping the US from building military
bases in Bangladesh because the U
because see India is 6t tall Pakistan is
2t tall Bangladesh is 1 ft tall but the
US is 28 ft
tall can we stop
them can we stop them they're too
powerful right now they are too
powerful says Why is everyone against
us? It feels so depressing. The US,
China, Pakistan, Bangladesh. It feels so
lonely. You see, there are 1.4 billion
of us. Why are you feeling
lonely? It's a privilege to have no
friends. It means you're doing something
right. It means everyone when everyone
is against you because they are jealous
of you. See the western world is jealous
of India. They occupied us and leeched
the lifeblood out of us for 250 years
and we still exist and we don't just
exist, we are rising again. They hate
that. The West is against us. No
question about it. They're not happy
about our progress, our growth. The
Chinese the same reason. They didn't
occupy us. They didn't leech our life
blood life us. But they have a very
Abrahamic mindset today. the Chinese
Communist Party and they see us as the
only nation in Eurasia apart from Russia
that can challenge them. That's why the
thing Pakistan, Bangladesh, well, we
know why they hate us. Okay, fine. But
I'll tell you what, my
friends, nobody else is against us. The
nations of the so-called global south,
they don't hate us. They would love to
see us rise. It will be such a it'll be
such a relief for them to have a nation
like India rise. Do you think Thailand
hates us? No. Do you think Indonesia
hates us? Are they against us? They're
not against us. They'll be happy to see
India rise because we are not a threat
and we'll be able to give them more
safety than any other predatory
hegemonic nation. Even the UAE and Saudi
Arabia are happy about India's growth.
So I would say that look at the world in
a different way. It's not that everybody
is against us. Lots of countries are
happy about India's growth. Look at all
the African nations. Do you think
anybody's against us there? Nobody is.
It's only certain specific countries
that are super jealous of our our
continuing existence about the fact that
we still have our culture. They haven't
been able to destroy it. And the fact
that we are again standing up and now
especially after what we've done to
Pakistan, they'll be super jealous and
seething. It's a privilege to have
people who are jealous of you. It means
you're doing something right. And please
remember there are 1.4 billion of us. So
don't feel like we are lonely. We are
not lonely. We have each other. What
else do we need? We have each other. All
of us. 1.4 billion of
us. Uh Jack Sparrow is saying, "Don't
scold me." I don't mean to scold you. I
don't mean to scold you at all. He was
trying to say gain some knowledge and
can nukes be intercepted after being
fired after. No, no, no. Absolutely not.
Sometimes I get annoyed and all, but
it's nothing personal. And I the only
reason I'm doing all this is is so I can
interact with you all and whatever
little understanding I have, I can share
it with you all. So uh so if I came
across it like I'm scolding you, I don't
I didn't mean to do that and you are
very welcome to ask as many questions as
you want and there are no stupid
questions. This is the only way we
learn. So please go
ahead. Okay. Jaspit Singh says as we
know the defense minister of Pakistan
has admitted the hand the hands behind
the terrorism are of UK of the US and
the UK Britain though we know that can
we now condemn the US in front of the
world we
can't uh officially we can't
um they're too powerful right
now so we will not talk about that they
have been behind Pakistani terrorism
they have funded and financed Pakistani
terrorism the mastermind of the U of the
Mumbai attacks 2008 was an American
citizen who is an American prison right
now. We have an extradition treaty with
them but they won't hand him over
because they have something to
hide. So everyone knows the whole world
knows but the whole world tries to
disregard what's what's come out in in
public. The Pakistani uh fig leaf of
plausible deniability is gone. Long
gone. It's gone.
But because the Americans are so
powerful, we will not speak about this
as of now. Because like I say, like I
keep saying in this episode, we are 6t
tall, but they are 28 ft tall and you
can't mess with them right now. So let
us grow. Let us become 30 ft tall, 50 ft
tall, then we'll talk. We'll see. All
right. Okay.
Samrat Shukla says what should India do
within our borders Kashmir especially to
fight against terrorism as terrorists
get internal support also like logistics
manpower communication etc. We need to
identify all these networks. All these
networks within India. All the enemies
within who support terrorism. We need to
identify all the enemies within who
support our enemies outside of India.
And we need to deal with them in full
complete accordance with the laws of the
country. Right? That's what needs to do.
You have raised a very important point.
Um there are so many overground workers
who seem to have been involved in what
happened in Palgam and beyond that there
are 100 million possibly Bangladeshes
all across India embedded in every nook
and cranny and corner of India. You
think they are our friends? They're
foreigners. They have no allegiance to
our our land, to our culture, to our to
our civilization, to our country. The
moment they get a chance, they'll do
something against us. What about the
other foreigners on our territory? the
cookies, the Rohhingyas, the Pakistanis
and God knows who
else. You have to evict them all. We
need to start a mass deportation
program. Once the foreigners are
deported, we need to look at the enemies
within the citizens who are enemies
within. There's a bunch of those also
apparently. So, all of that needs to be
done. Only then can we have uh safety
within the
country.
Okay. Um Bendra says, "I told India and
Pakistan that if you stop the war, we
will do trade, a lot of trade with you.
If you don't, we will not trade. All of
a sudden, they stopped. Yeah, he said
that. He said that and I put it out on
the screen some time ago. Let me share
that again. In the beginning of today's
live stream, I put that on the screen.
Check this
out. Here we have it. Uh, so he claimed
that US trade leverage played a role in
diffusion tensions between the two
countries, saying that we helped a lot.
We also helped with trade. I said, "Come
on, we're going to do a lot of trade
with you guys. Let's stop it. Let's stop
it. If you stop it, we're doing trade.
If you don't stop it, we're not going to
do any trade." So, he's essentially
threatened India with trade sanctions.
Essentially, he's threatened India with
sanctions that we will I will destroy
your economy. That's what he did to
us. Don't forget that. Don't forget what
he has
done. Okay.
Okay, Universe says uh nuclear blackmail
won't work practically. How? They are
crazy guys. Even this time probably they
got out by saying that to Trump. If they
threat if they or if they act, how do we
handle? Look, if they wanted to act,
they would have acted because we had
them on their knees. We hit nine
Pakistani air bases, the best air bases
they had in 30
minutes. We had destroyed everything,
all the air defenses. By that time if
you still don't use the your nuclear
weapons when will you use it right so
it's their nuclear blackmail is hollow
they would have obviously threatened
threatened Trump with nuclear
retaliation or whatever that they will
launch nuclear weapons on India but yeah
it's all hollow and we have air defenses
that that can take out all these
missiles so don't worry the so much we
have our air defenses are the best in
the world today better than the Israeli
iron dome we have proven it so let's not
worry about the Pakistani nuclear threat
One second. Where was
this? H questions just fly
away. All right. All right. Give me a
second. Give me a second. Give me a
second. Fire. Pause. Are we going to How
are we going to take back P? Are we
going to threaten by nuclear escalation?
It's not like Pakistan is going to lose
their nukes. Let's uh keep P for later.
I suppose we're supposed to take it back
in the next two three days or the past 2
three days. We'll see about that. We'll
see about it. We'll talk about it when
it when when the time comes to it.
Okay. Uh Shri Watsu says India doesn't
seem to buy any German technology even
though Germany has ultra ad even though
Germany was ultra advanced during the
Second World War. Why is that? It's
because the Germans are US vessels and
they will not sell us their good their
best technology. They have good
submarines have good good stuff
but the the Germans don't have a very
good attitude towards India.
It's it's visible if you know where to
look. So it's it's not a good idea to
buy German technology. They have good
technology for
sure. Okay. Archa says how are citizens
of Pakistan how are the citizens of
Pakistan not aware of what their nation
is doing? I mean do not do they not see
international media to know the truth uh
and so on. I'm sure the citizens of
Pakistan know what their nation is doing
and they are fine with it. This is what
Indians don't understand. Indians think
that the Pakistanis are like us,
reasonable people. We don't hate
Pakistan. We don't want we don't wish
death and destruction on the people of
Pakistan. So we assume that the
Pakistanis are just like us. Dear
brothers and sisters of Pakistan, you
are just like us. Is it is it true? The
truth is the Pakistanis are our blood.
No question. They are our flesh and
blood. Same blood, same DNA, same
ancestors.
But I am certain at least 90% of
Pakistan's citizens want us
dead. And they're okay with lying and
cheating and whatever to have us dead.
They are indoctrinated in that way. They
see us as the enemy. They want us dead.
If there's a terror attack on India,
they like it. They celebrate
it. Maybe 5 10% of Pakistanis don't hate
us. And and I'm glad there are such
people that exist. But the overwhelming
majority of Pakistan's population hates
us. They want us dead. They celebrate
terror attacks on us. They know what
their nation is doing. And even when
their nation loses, they want to say
that we have won. And they support their
ISI. They support their military. They
support their
terrorists. They call their terrorists
freedom fighters. They call their
terrorists social workers. They know
everything that's happening.
It's not like they don't know what's
happening. Please, we need to disabuse
ourselves of this delusional thoughts of
this delusional um u this delusion that
the Pakistanis are like us and they they
both sides of the border want things to
be well. No, they don't. They want us
destroyed. They want us destroyed.
Please understand that. Those of those
Pakistanis who don't want us destroyed,
I'm glad they exist. Of course, some
some of them do. There must be 5 10% of
Pakistanis who don't want us dead. The
overwhelming majority of them want us
dead. They want to see us bleed. So,
please stop loving Pakistanis to hell
with them. Most of
them. Okay. Something skeptic says again
Pakistan attacked India. Well, well,
well, well. We need to do something
about this these Pakistanis. Teach them
a lesson they'll not forget. Uh let's
see. Let's see. That's for the
government to look into. Okay. Vira says
if Pakistan have said that they have
been indulging in terrorism for the US,
why is the US still helping them?
Shouldn't they be against Pakistan? No.
Because you see the world is not like
this all goody goody nice nice. If the
US has been helping
Pakistan, has been using Pakistan as as
the terrorist nation for their own
benefit, why will they stop helping
them? It it
See Pakistan has admitted we have been
doing terrorism for 30 40 whatever years
for the US. It means that the US if this
claim is true has an interest in
terrorism and wants Pakistan to use
terrorism as a an instrument of state
policy to advance American geopolitical
interests.
So if their interests are such that
these interests needs need terrorism to
be achieved then why will they stop all
this? Why will they go against Pakistan?
Pakistan has been a good doggy for them.
Good nice doggy. You've been doing
whatever I wanted. You're my attack dog.
Why will I suddenly go against
him? Doesn't make sense. Right.
Logically, right?
uh some questions I will not take. I
don't want to get into more
controversies for
unnecessarily. Let whoever wants to say
whatever let them say
it. Okay. Minora says don't the
Pakistani army feel shame after losing
they don't accept
loss and they have the audacity to say
they won. See from their perspective
they are fighting the just a just war
and it is said that if something is
worth fighting for it is worth fighting
dirty for and that is something we
should learn from the
Pakistanis. We are all all about satya
jay the truth has to be told. No if your
nation is worth fighting for. It is
worth lying for. It is worth cheating
for. It is worth stealing for. It is
worth fighting dirty for. Please learn
this from your adversaries.
Please. We need to learn these things
even from our
enemies. Okay. Money assures us huge
drones attacked by Pakistan in several
places of Punjab and Jammu. Enough is
enough. I say enough is enough. I I
agree with you. But uh let's see what
the government does about this. I I
definitely say enough is enough. Okay,
let us take maybe one more question.
Let's take one more question. Where do
we take it?
Uh
the one second I was trying to take some
question. It flew
away. Uh I think this is that clown who
I used to kind of like whose way of
moving attention from his various
blenders like tariffs which wiped out
$10 trillion economies from the market.
Yeah, Trump may be trying to divert
attention away from his failures.
Possibly. Possibly. Roshan says after PM
Modi's comment that terrorists and
Pakistani army will be treated as equal
will India declare Pakistan army a
terrorist organization. Our actions
should declare Pakistan a terrorist
organization. Our actions should equate
the Pakistani army with terrorists.
Forget about words. Indians are obsessed
with words. Let's stop obsessing with
words. Our actions should tell the world
that we consider the Pakistani army to
be the same as the Pakistani terrorists.
Our actions should speak louder than our
words. All right. Okay. Thank you so
much for all your questions. I'm going
to end the live stream at this point in
time. Thank you so much. I know lots of
you have questions, but I got to end it
here. So, I will see you very soon in
the next live stream. Possibly tomorrow.
I'll decide tomorrow. Okay. Possibly
tomorrow. We'll see. We'll see about
that. Anyway, thank you so much. Take
care and I will see you soon in the next
one.